Kotschnig, Walter Maria; Papers ger053
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Pamphlets, 1922-1978; 10; 136 items
  - Pamphlets dealing with European Student Relief, International Student Service, World Student Service Fund, and World Student Relief, 1922-1945; 10.1 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 1-30)
    - Résolutions de la Conférence d'Elmau. Réunie sous les auspices de l'Entr'aide Universitaire (Fédération Universelle des Associations Chrétiennes d'Etudiants), 14-31 Juillet 1924, Elmau, Allemagne (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 3)
    - Rapports des Commissions. Quatrième Conférence Annuelle de l'Entr'Aide Universitaire de la Fédération Universelle des Associations Chrétiennes d'Etudiants, Genève-Gex, 4-12 Août 1925 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 4)
    - Quatrième Conférence Annuelle de l'Entr'Aide Universitaire, Genève-Gex, Août 4-12 1925 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 5)
    - Annual Report on International Student Service (formerly European Student Relief) of the World's Student Christian Federation July 1, 1924-July 1, 1925 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 6)
    - Fünfte Jahrestagung des Weltstudentenwerkes des Christlichen Studenten Weltbundes, Karlowitz, Jugoslavien, 24. Juli-2. August, 1926 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 7)
    - Annual Report for the college year 1925-1926 of International Student Service of the World's Student Christian Federation (Formerly European Student Relief) (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 8)
    - Sixth Annual Conference of International Student Service of the World's Student Christian Federation. A Report on the Speeches, Discussions and Commissions of the Conference, Schiers - Switzerland, August 6th-15th, 1927 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 9)
    - The Chartres Conference and the future of International Student Service. Report of the VIIth Annual Conference (Collaborators' Conference) of I.S.S. August 1928 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 10)
    - L'Entr'Aide Universitaire Internationale en 1929 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 11)
    - Student Service in Five Continents, 1929 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 12)
    - A New Decade. Report of the Ninth Annual Conference of International Student Service, Oxford, July 23-31, 1930 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 13)
    - Annual Report on International Student Service 1929-1930 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 14)
    - The University in a Changing World, being a report of the Tenth Annual Conference held from Aug. 31st to Sept. 9th, 1931 at Mount Holyoke College, Mass., U.S.A. (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 15)
    - "The Students in the Social Order". Report of the Eleventh Annual Conference of International Student Service. Brno, Czechoslovakia, July 27th-August 3rd, 1932 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 16)
    - International Student Service issues its final appeal on behalf of German Refugee Students, 1936 November (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 17)
    - A Report on the work of relief and reconstruction for German Refugee Students by the co-operating committee for England & Wales of International Student Service (May 1933-August 1937), 1937 July (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 18)
    - International Student Service. A Three Years Plan. 1937, 1938, 1939 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 19)
    - International Student Service. Annual Report. 1936-1937 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 20)
    - International Student Service. A Brief Report of the Year 1936-37, 1937 July (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 21)
    - International Student Service. Annual Report. 1937-38, 1938 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 22)
    - International Student Service. What It Is .... What It Does ...., 1938-1939 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 23)
    - Selection and Furthering of Gifted Students. Report of a Conference between university people from nine countries, organized by International Student Service; Hindsgavl, Denmark; 26th-30th May 1939 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 24)
    - The Student's Part in a Troubled World. A Report of Service Abroad, [1940] (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 25)
    - Students in Europe Must Live! A First Report on War Relief Activities April 1940-March 1941 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 26)
    - Camp-ISS-Bello. An Account of the First ISS Summer Student Leadership Institute Held at Campobello, New Brunswick, Canada, June 30 to August 2, 1941 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 27)
    - Students and the Peace. A first approach to the problems of University Relief and Rehabilitation. Report of a Conference held at Oxford, July 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 28)
    - The Story of World Student Relief 1937-1943. A Report to the Constituency of the World Student Service Fund, 1943 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 29)
    - Serving Students in War-Time China 1937-1944. World Student Relief (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 30)
  - Unauthored pamphlets, general, 10.2 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets))
    - A Community Program Guide. Drug Abuse Prevention, 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 31)
    - A Federal Source Book: Answers to the most frequently asked questions about drugs, 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 32)
    - A Year of Development. Highlights from the Report of the Administrator on the United States Development Programme in 1977, 1978 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 33)
    - Commitments of U.S. Power Abroad. Issues in United States Foreign Policy, No. 3, 1969 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 34)
    - The Covenant of the League of Nations. With amendments in Force October 1936, Undated (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 35)
    - Drug Abuse, 1971 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 36)
    - For a Free Austria in a Free World. A Report on the Austrian Situation, [1942] (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 37)
    - Ideology and Reality in the Soviet System. (Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, XCIX, No. 1), 1955 January 27 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 38)
    - The I.L.O. and Plans for a "People's Peace". The London Meeting of the Emergency Committee, April 1942, 1942 July (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 39)
    - The International Bureau of Education in 1942-1943. Report of the Director (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 40)
    - International Development Strategy. Action Programme of the General Assembly of the Second United Nations Development Decade, 1970 December (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 41)
    - International Labour Conference. Twenty-sixth Session. The Organisation of Employment in the Transition from War to Peace, 1944 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 42)
    - International Narcotics Control. An excerpt from ... United States Foreign Policy 1972. A Report of the Secretary of State, 1973 May (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 43)
    - Man-Power Mobilisation for Peace, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 44)
    - Multilateral Disarmament and the Special Session. Twelfth Conference on the United Nations of the Next Decade. San Juan del Rio, Mexico, June 19-25, 1977 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 45)
    - Negotiation and Statecraft. A Selection of Readings, 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 46)
    - Pakistan, 1948 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 47)
    - Pre-investment and Productivity, 1967 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 48)
    - Program. Closing Plenary Session. The United Nations Conference on International Organization. San Francisco, June 26, 1945 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 49)
    - The Public Looks at World Organization. National Opinion Research Center Report No. 19, 1944 April (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 50)
    - Public Speaking On Drug Abuse Prevention: A Handbook for the Law Enforcement Officer, 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 51)
    - Report of the President's Commission for the observance of the twenty-fifth anniversary of the United Nations, 1971 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 52)
    - The SALT Process, 1978 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 53)
    - Statistics of State and Local Teacher Retirement Systems, 1943-44, 1945 April (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 54)
    - Student Victims of War. Blackout of Education, [1940] (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 55)
    - The Technical Cooperation Programs of the United Nations System. A Report of the Advisory Committee on International Organizations, 1963 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 56)
    - Too Busy to Shoot Heroin. A Complete Program, 1971 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 57)
    - United Nations. Issues in United States Foreign Policy No. 5, 1970 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 58)
    - The United Nations, an excerpt from ... U.S. Foreign Policy for the 1970s. Building for Peace. A Report To The Congress By Richard Nixon, President of the United States, 1971 February 25 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 59)
    - The United Nations Development Decade at Mid-Point. An Appraisal by the Secretary-General, 1965 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 60)
    - The United States and the United Nations. Report of the United States Delegation to the First Part of the First Session of the General Assembly of the United Nations, London, England, January 10-February 14, 1946 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 61)
    - The University's Role in the Development of the Third World. The Proceedings of a World University Service Symposium, 1966 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 62)
    - U.S. Foreign Assistance In The 1970s: A New Approach. Report To The President From The Task Force On International Development, March 4, 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 63)
    - War and Peace Aims. Extracts from Statements of United Nations Leaders. Special Supplement No. 1 to the United Nations Review, 1943 January 30 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 64)
    - "We, the peoples ... A Brief History of the United Nations, 1947 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 65)
    - What Should Be Done with Conquered Germany?, [1943] (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 66)
    - You and your fuel oil ration. The Why and How of Fuel Oil Rationing and What To Do About It!, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 67)
  - Authored pamphlets, 10.3 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets))
    - The American Friends of German Freedom.Germany Tomorrow, [1941] (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 68)
    - Asher, Robert E.Multilateral Versus Bilateral Aid: An Old Controversy Revisited, 1963 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 69)
    - Benes, Vojta.A Proposal for the Reconstruction of the Educational System in Post-War Central and Eastern Europe, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 70)
    - Benton, William.How Far can UNESCO Reach? A "Point 5" Program for Peace, 1950 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 71)
    - Benton, William.Where We Are: And Where Are We Going?, 1948 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 72)
    - Benton, William.Why More Businessmen should be Democrats, 1956 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 73)
    - Berg, Dorothy F.Illicit Use of Dangerous Drugs in the United States: A Compilation of Studies, Surveys, and Polls, 1970 September (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 74)
    - Bloomfield, Lincoln P.; Charles W. Yost.What Future for the UN? An Atlantic Dialogue, 1977 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 75)
    - Braisted, Paul J.International Exchange of Students and Scholars, 1943 December (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 76)
    - British Information Services.The Future of Education in England and Wales, 1944 August (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 77)
    - Brown, George F. Jr.; Lester R. Silverman.The Retail Price of Heroin: Estimation & Applications, 1973 May (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 78)
    - Bureau of Narcotics & Dangerous Drugs.drugs of abuse, Undated (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 79)
    - Bureau of Narcotics & Dangerous Drugs.Teen-age Booby Trap, 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 80)
    - Burnet, Mary.The mass media in a violent world, 1971 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 81)
    - Charles, Enid.The Effect of Present Trends in Fertility and Mortality upon the Future Population of England and Wales and upon its Age Composition, 1935 August (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 82)
    - Cohen, Felix S.The Social and Economic Consequences of Exclusionary Immigration Laws, 1939 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 83)
    - Cohn, Alfred E.; Stephen Duggan; Harry D. Gideonse; Dorothy Paley.A Memorandum on the Need for A New Journal on Higher Education in the United States, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 84)
    - Cohrssen, John J.The Organization of the United Nations to Deal with Drug Abuse, 1973 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 85)
    - Comité Interministériel des problèmes médicaux et sociaux scolaires.informations sur la "drogue", ca. 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 86)
    - Comité Soviétique de la Défense de la Paix.Problèmes du Desarmement - point de vue soviétique, 1978 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 87)
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.Fifth Report. Security and Disarmament Under the United Nations, 1947 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 88)
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.Guide to Community Activity on Human Rights, 1946 May (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 89)
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.Uniting the Nations for Health, [1946] (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 90)
    - Committee on Human Rights, Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.Draft. International Bill of Human Rights, 1947 February (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 91)
    - Culbertson, Ely.A System to Win this War and to win the peace to come. The World Federation Plan, 1942 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 92)
    - The Drug Abuse Council, Inc.A Perspective on "Get Tough" Drug Laws, 1973 March (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 93)
    - Duckworth-Barker, Vernon.Breakthrough to tomorrow. The story of International Co-operation for Development through the United Nations, 1970 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 94)
    - Eichelberger, Clark M.The United Nations Charter. What Was Done at San Francisco, 1945 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 95)
    - Elliott, William Yandel; H. Duncan Hall (eds.).The British Commonwealth of Nations in War and Peace, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 96)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica Educational Corporation.The Drug Scene. Fact not Fiction, 1971 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 97)
    - Gideonse, Harry D.The Present Chaos in Education, 1939 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 98)
    - Gross, Feliks.The Decline of European Culture And Its Reconstruction, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 99)
    - Halecki, Oskar.Intellectual Cooperation in the Post-War World, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 100)
    - Harms, Bernhard.Universitäten, Professoren und Studenten in der Zeitenwende. Vornehmlich vom Standpunkt der Staatswissenschaft, 1936 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 101)
    - Hill, Martin.The Administrative Committee on Co-ordination, Undated; Reprint (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 102)
    - Hiss, Donald.United States Participation in The United Nations. A Study of the Methods and Mechanisms Used in the Formulation and Coordination of Policies Proposed by the United States, 1947 November (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 103)
    - Hunt, Leon Gibson.Heroin Epidemics: A Quantitative Study of Current Empirical Data, 1973 May (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 104)
    - Knox, Raymond C.New Faith in Reason, 1939 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 105)
    - Kosygin, Alexei.Directives for the Five-Year Economic Development Plan of the USSR for 1971-1975 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 106)
    - Kozak, J. B.Democratic Ideas in Postwar Education in Central and Eastern Europe (Sociological Survey), 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 107)
    - League of Nations.The Development of International Co-operation in Economic and Social Affairs. Report of the Special Committee, 1939 August (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 108)
    - Leland, Waldo G.International Cultural Relations, 1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 109)
    - Leybourne, Grace G.A New Charter for Education, 1942 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 110)
    - McKitterick, Nathaniel M.U.S. Diplomacy in the Development Agencies of the United Nations, 1934 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 111)
    - McNamara, Robert S.Address to the Board of Governors, 1977 September 26 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 112)
    - Michanek, Ernst.For and against the Welfare State. Swedish Experiences, 1964 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 113)
    - Milam, Carl H.Report of the Executive Secretary, 1942-1943 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 114)
    - Montefiore, L. G.The Spirit of the German Universities, Undated (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 115)
    - Morehouse, Ward.Science, Technology, and the Global Equity Crisis: New Directions for United States Policy, 1978 May (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 116)
    - Nagasaki Preparatory Committee for International Symposium on the Damage and After-Effects of the Atomic Bombing of Hiroshima and Nagasaki.Report from Nagasaki On the Damage and After-Effects of the Atomic Bombing, 1978 February 15 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 117)
    - National Resources Planning Board.Post-War Agenda. Full Employment. Security. Building America, 1942 November (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 118)
    - Perham, Margery.African Facts and American Criticisms, 1944 April; Reprint (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 119)
    - Progressive Education Association.Democratic Education. Suggestions for Education and National Defense, 1940 October (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 120)
    - Rees, Elfan.Century of the Homeless Man, 1957 November (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 121)
    - Rehrmann, Leslie Beckett.The World Youth Movement, 1945 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 122)
    - Schurmann, Carl W. A.A Center For International Fact Finding: A Review and a Proposal, 1963 July (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 123)
    - Smith, T. V.On Being Retired, 1956 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 124)
    - Stinebower, Leroy D.The Economic and Social Council. An Instrument of International Cooperation, 1945 (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 125)
    - Studebaker, John W.The New National Occupational Information and Guidance Service, 1938; Reprint (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 126)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.LSD. Some Questions and Answers, 1969 March (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 127)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.Marihuana. Some Questions and Answers, 1969 March (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 128)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.Narcotics. Some Questions and Answers, 1969 March (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 129)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.The Up and Down Drugs. Amphetamines and Barbituates, 1969 March (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 130)
    - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Problem III: Treatment of Defeated Enemy Countries. Germany, 1943 March (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 131)
    - Vambery, Rustem.The Hungarian Problem, 1942 May (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 132)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison.Shall We Rule Germany?, 1943 June (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 133)
    - Winslow, Anne.Toward Freedom From Want. Handbook on the United Nations Economic and Social Council and Specialized Agencies, 1947 March (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 134)
    - Winslow, C.-E. A.International Organization for Health, 1944 April (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 135)
    - Winston, Henry Merritt.Subsoil of Peace, 1942 July (Box 22 (10-Pamphlets), Folder 136)